They just walked out of there!
Yeah, I know,
I was sort of sitting next to you.
The whole Waters family.
They just walked right out of there!
Again, I was in the room.
How do they always manage that?!
They're good.
They're greedy
and they'll do it again,
and next time we're going to
catch them in the act.
How?
No good?
They always know we're coming.
How do they always know?!
They're good, they work at it.
They're never going to stop.
Well, neither are we.
Argh!
Argh! AARGH!
Oh! Greg...
In the act!
It's the only way we're going to
do this, in the act!
They're still blocking it?
Yeah. Very efficiently hacked.
They must be bloody pleased
with themselves.
They must be.
Right then?
Ah, no! No, you've got to make
the arrest. This one's yours, boss.
You've never called me boss before.
Oh, well, look what happens
when you're good.
You know how most days
aren't good days?
This is a good day. Not
for the Waters family.
OK, ten men on the roof,
all exits covered.
The bank's closed, so we've
no hostages to worry about.
Sorry, no, go on. Go on.
Um, we've got the tunnel
entrance covered...
...and Davies, Willow and Christie
are heading up armed
response on Mafeking Road.
Sorry, I'd better get this.
It's him, isn't it?
I, I, I have to go. What?!
You make the arrest. No way!
Sorry, you'll be fine.
I'm cool with this.
Jones will get all the credit
if you leave now, you know he will.
Yeah, well, yeah, it doesn't matter,
I have to go.
Back up! I need maximum back up!
Baker Street now!
What's going on?!
This is hard. What?
Really hard.
Hardest thing I've ever had to do.
Do you know any funny stories
about John?
What?!
I need anecdotes.
Didn't go to any trouble, did you?
Shut up, Mrs Hudson.
I haven't said a word.
You're formulating a question,
it's physically painful
watching you think.
I thought it was you playing.
It was me playing.
I am composing.
You were dancing.
I was road-testing.
You what?
Why are you here?
I'm bringing you your morning tea.
You're not usually awake.
You bring me tea in the morning?
Well, where do you think
it came from?
I don't know.
I just thought it sort of happened.
Your mother has a lot to answer for.
Hmm, I know. I have a list.
Mycroft has a file.
So, it's the big day then.
What big day?
The wedding! John and Mary
getting married.
Two people who currently live
together are about to attend church,
have a party, go on a short holiday,
then carry on living together.
What's big about that?
It changes people, marriage.
Hmm, no it doesn't.
Well, you wouldn't understand,
cos you always live alone.
Your husband was executed
for double murder.
You're hardly an advert
for companionship.
Marriage changes you as a person
in ways that you can't imagine.
As does lethal injection.
My best friend, Margaret,
she was my chief bridesmaid,
we were going to be best friends
forever, we always said that,
but I hardly saw her after that.
Aren't there usually biscuits?
I've run out. Have the shops?
She cried the whole day, saying,
"Ooh, it's the end of an era."
I'm sure the shop
on the corner is open.
She was probably right, really.
I remember she left early.
I mean, who leaves a wedding early?
So sad.
Hmm. Anyway, you've got
things to do.
No, not really. I've got plenty of
time to get ready... Biscuits!
Oh! I really am going to
have a word with your mother.
You can if you like,
she understands very little.
Right then.
Into battle.
Congratulations!
OK, hold it there, I want to get
this shot of the newlyweds.
Er, just the bride and groom,
please.
Sherlock...
Oh, sorry.
OK, three, two, one, cheese.
The famous Mr Holmes.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
But no sex, OK? Sorry?!
You don't have to look so scared,
I'm only messing.
Bridesmaid, best man,
it's a bit traditional.